let questionList = [
  {
    question: "1 + 1?",
    ans: "2",
    options: ["3", "2", "1", "0"]
  },
  {
    question: "5 - 3?",
    ans: "2",
    options: ["1", "2", "3", "0"]
  },
  {
    question: "3 x 2?",
    ans: "6",
    options: ["5", "6", "4", "3"]
  },
  {
    question: "8 รท 2?",
    ans: "4",
    options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"]
  },
  {
    question: "10 - 7?",
    ans: "3",
    options: ["2", "3", "4", "1"]
  },
  {
    question: "6 + 4?",
    ans: "10",
    options: ["9", "10", "11", "8"]
  },
  {
    question: "9 รท 3?",
    ans: "3",
    options: ["2", "3", "4", "1"]
  },
  {
    question: "7 - 5?",
    ans: "2",
    options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"]
  },
  {
    question: "4 x 2?",
    ans: "8",
    options: ["6", "7", "8", "9"]
  },
  {
    question: "12 รท 4?",
    ans: "3",
    options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"]
  }
];
